spoono.com 2003-12-02

# Spoono - Privacy Policy

Spoono has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

### COLLECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-in and remove themselves from receiving our newsletter and other communications at the point where we request information about the visitor. Any information collected will not be shared or used for any other purpose than receiving information from Spoono.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website.

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address).

None of the personal information collected by Spoono will ever be shared with any third party company without consent from the user.

### COOKIES

Most areas of Spoono use cookies to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server (such as a file the keeps track of a user's flavor/style preferences). Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

### THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING

We use Google's AdSense program to serve ads when you visit our website. Google may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

### THIRD PARTY COOKIES

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

### CORRECT/UPDATE

Spoono gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. Remove or change your infomation from our database at the place of data collection.
  2. Email [webmaster@spoono.com](mailto:webmaster@spoono.com).

### CONTACTING SPOONO

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you may contact: 

_Spoono, LLC  
Spoono  
106 Michelle Circle  
Bethel Park, PA 15102_

Fax: 412-831-5077
